# **ADIL TAHIRI**

Software Engineer

#### SUMMARY

Experienced software engineer with a deep interest in AI. with two years of experience. and successfully do front and back-end web applications. Looking to bring my skills life to a tech company. I believe there is so much more I can achieve with dedication and skill

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Software Engineer at 100devs

January 2022 — Present

- Collaborated with a team of developers to build modern and responsive web applications using best practices
- Built semantically structured with my team in full stack web applications

#### Freelance in front-end

December 2019 — Present

I build a web application for my client to do more stuff to get an experience like contribute with an open-source and practice my knowledge to challenge myself a do problem-solving

## **Recent Projects**

### Amina salon (Full stack Web App):

This website builds to make anyone can reach and contact the shop owner and reserve without going to a salon shop and you can check the price and type of sty you want.

## special tour (Full stack Web App):

special tour is a website that shows you the meaning of adventure and explores the word and gives you some excitement to go see it by yourself

### Sami Food delivery & restaurant (Full Stack Web App)

SamiFood is a small restaurant and food delivery the meaning of this website is to take a look at the food they offer and where the location is and to reserve a table or order the food from home built with react tailwind firebase and more.

## Other Projects:

#### 100Hours Project:

Process bucket is full stack app build with JavaScript, NodeJS, mongo dB, CSS, OAuth, and more. I developed a personal finance management website that allows users to track their expenses and view spending patterns through customizable breakdowns on a daily, weekly, monthly, or yearly basis. The dashboard offers clear and visually engaging charts and graphs while implementing robust authentication protocols to protect sensitive user data. Overall, my work on this website demonstrates my skills in full-stack web development, data processing, and UI/UX design.

#### CONTACT

+212-676538776

Rajaadil19952012@gmail.co

Website

GitHub

LinkedIn

@aadilth

### **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

Node

MongoDB

test

Web Accessibility

API

A11<sub>y</sub>

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Université Cadi Ayyad

2014 - 2018

Major:

#### Languages

Arabic

English

French